Juan Sebastian Gonzalez

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT

 \bigvee

jsebastiangb.12@gmail.com



Cel: 3002069768



linkedin.com/in/juansebastiangonzalezb/



Cali, Colombia



github.com/JuanSebastianGB

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Python
- Javascript
- ReactJS
- Node.is
- Git and Github
- Mysql
- HTML/CSS

SOFT SKILLS

- Team Work
- Adaptability
- Self Learning
- Discipline

LANGUAGE

- Spanish Native.
- English Conversational

ABOUT ME

Software engineer with 4 years of professional experience as a biomedical engineer creating and managing a system for the persistence of information associated with the traceability and life cycle of biomedical technology.

Looking to contribute backend and frontend skillsets to a company impacting process optimization using technologies such as Javascript and Python.

Bash and Linux preferred proficiency in Docker.

EDUCATION

• Holberton School

WebStack - FullStack Developer | Apr. 2022 - Current

Holberton School

Software Developer | Jun 2021 - Mar. 2022 Holberton School

- Universidad Autonoma de Occidente Electromedicine and hospital technology management| Jun. 2015
- Universidad Autonoma de Occidente Biomedical Engineer | Oct. 2014

PROJECTS

Mar 2022 - Apr 2022 **AHORRA APP**

Full Stack project to handle personal Spends and Savings.

Front

React and CSS with Google Auth to handle the login.

Back

Python implementing FastAPI to get customized documentation using Swagger, and strict typing validation.

Database

A relational database (SQL database) was implemented to handle persistent data, adding a logic layer using SQLAlchemy as ORM to serve a full REST API.

DevOps

The whole project was implemented with CI/CD using docker-compose and docker hub as DevOps implementation.

Deploy

The project was deployed in a digital ocean dropplet to serve as web service both, Front and Back

https://github.com/SandraCalero/AhorrApp.git

Nov 2021 - Feb 2022

AIRBNB CLONE

Created a clone of Web site AirBNB Developed in Python in the code base, using Flask and Jinja as frameworks to perform Back and Front, and Javascript to specific interactions in the front. The project was created in different stages, such as a custom console, web static design, Database with the option to switch between MySQL and JSON files as storage, Deploy static, web framework, RESTFUL API, and Web dynamic. And Overall implementing unit testing.

https://github.com/JuanSebastianGB/AirBnB_clone https://github.com/JuanSebastianGB/AirBnB_clone_v2 https://github.com/afecego/AirBnB_clone_v3 https://github.com/manolobkno08/AirBnB_clone_v4

Aug 2021 - Sep 2021 SIMPLE SHELL

Created a simple command-line interpreter with C that read commands from standard input and performs the corresponding execution. This simple_shell is a simplified version of sh and implements standard functions and system calls like: execve, exit, fork, getline, malloc, perror, stat, wait, write.

https://github.com/mateog91/simple_shell

EXPERIENCE

- Biomedical Engineer HUV, | 2019-current Create a lamp stack project to handle the inventory of medical devices. Performing administrative tasks related to the traceability of medical devices., and management related to clinical engineering.
- Statistician. IPTL | Nov 2017-Dic 2018 Digitizing and analyzing information regarding telephone damage service orders. Using Custom company software and advanced excel.
- Tecnovigilancia leader.

HUV | Feb 2017-Oct 2017

Implement from zero the program to risk management of

medical devices in "Hospital Universitario del Valle"